I got the question, but we all think it's 100
.  All over the world external sex the rinse is done in the era, the market
instead blows up a kind of super kind of tablets out.  What blow you back to Hong Kong
yeah feed, you know what
to it.  Today I to two podcast introduction blind people
, one is from the big crazy sweep are suddenly decent oriental,
which person is you want to erect is strong.
Feed, he has a better sun year.  Another uncle and talented publisher
Jin, in his next grains are the voice of the king, used to see
s, as a person to live creative life test win big things, the way is
to turn around faster, they in the real world all the way to
find a balance, and to make sense, and to find
, maybe I have to spend 100,000 dollars, not necessarily commercial benefits
ah, do not know, at least I have to think, so
I do not like to explain this, so I like this, so I did not like this
Please share your experience, how much do you have on the government side.  Is that what you
hate the most, yes, most, many people think business is the number
, but in fact the top creativity instead is to embrace the number of counts of the
brigade, if the count is right, then everyone can
count that number, no one can count that number.  Are you
welcome to watch on your heart, we this episode is just talk,
we do not talk about the heart of so, because this, we invited two
national-level uncles up, is we have Golden City, we
have Eastern Star, in fact, I think it is also the most in so many episodes
, because we know how to talk, is everyone is the
host.  It's not, you have to ask, yes, it's when you
sit down, actually I'm curious about one thing, is
actually how we are each other is to read the various words of the interview
, so I observed myself for example, I will see Jincheng like this
, Jincheng your programs, I see the department ah and outside very
different, wake up after putting back some.  The state is putting some back,
but participating in that guest, maybe he may not usually open his
mouth to say that type of thing, but you will ask it.  You
will come up not only that you will also ask him to open his mouth to talk about
a lot of inner world things, outside can not see, because I
do open magazine does that means two doors this kind of that that will ask some
guests to do interviews, is like at the same time that better by the way
shoot like this, so I should I have to invite guests that thing
is more that is natural d grow slowly so slowly but slowly so shoot
Another thing a little like this, have you thought about the approach of your interview
, because this, I think Hong Kong interviews, you did the
best, the reason is because of this you can ask some good
, is?  It's not a very pointed question, my analysis as an author
is because you have a good movie
, the question is easy I think it's very
ordinary, but you use a very objective, very
informative nature, and that person is willing to answer you, I think
this is a very sharp way of interviewing yeah, I think it is,
I do not know if there is good or not, first of all, I am not too digging
I used to say really young, for example
Emotional, I like to know each person's view the most
, that is, the thoughts of each thing, how to go about his thing
, I prefer this.  In fact, just before this Jincheng came up this
, I was with him, there we have an
observation, yes, you will receive yourself very small, that is, in the
interview, eh we its white very
participate in the conversation, and
you seem to be in an observing state, you put your own existence
so received the most actual then put to the maximum, than the guest,
you are like a psychiatrist.
For Lin that is very very safe so I can tell you.  I think it
's the characteristics of an editor, it's the characteristics of the editor who does the words in the writing room
.  It is to put yourself a little smaller, so taught
out is like this, before our social sensitivity is, our a
boss or what, even in the interview are my
word I should not.  There shouldn't be a word I, there should
be.  Third party scare, it should be like this, every time the interview is
that.  It's the
good thing about the interview, not the good thing about myself, I interviewed him, actually
.  The mindset is like this.  I feel
different.  For example, oriental sex, then my
feeling for you is that you will be very
flattering, and you will miss each other each other.  But you
are each other, however everyone is different there are, to have
.  And your way this is you will be
involved in his co-establishment of that
view, I don't know if this has a black design
or if he unintentionally appears as a character thing.  So I'm
pretty weird that you asked me to come I never think I'm good for interviews
, because I really satisfy my own curiosity about that person yeah
, curiosity about human nature.  So my interview, actually I
feed the awareness of a very strong self by asking him if it is true,
so I am very different from you,
so I appreciate you on I think you put very objective, and
I think I am too subjective, so it becomes the question what is it
?  What if I’m not interested in what that person does
?  I can't talk down.  I must have something to appreciate from the bottom of my heart
, something curious about him, I can do it.  I want to ask the
voice below how much of the year you interview people or when the you
started, I travel the world with very curious about people.  Um so I think it
starts with curiosity, even if a lot of the
interview?  I find some some people to work
, a little about the public, really in the end I became I
interview him, I was because I want to know, it turns out you worked in insurance
, that ancient industry has something, is I want me to gossip want to
know his industry, so I think that is actually
actually you curious, so I think this curiosity has always been there
.  I think it's me to share my own
experience, really I started doing podcast this show
actually not long, I still remember I was
very gradually scared at the beginning, and then, when I invited a guest up,
I actually had a perspective before, I really want to
understand him, slowly I did the fourth or fifth episode, I sometimes
may be in I think, oh,
I should ask what, like I should ask in the interview
fall down.  So I'm constantly nervous there, I'm going to scan the paper
yeah my research yeah and then I'm not listening
to the guest talking about it, maybe that's just what you said, is that it means
you're not interested enough in this.  If you are
not interested in this matter yourself, you can't have the intention to ask that, or
you can't be able to do it late.  So slowly I will
feel yeah, so from that day I am not going to
improve my own skills.  I was going to find
a right match for that so at that time I had
one like that to get.  But if you can do this thing,
you may not be so appreciative of it, is you have to that he
has to think about how to do it, you have to go very quickly.  To get to know this
person to understand him.  So Akin City and Oriental,
you are why you decided to do a human room in the first place, that was
once some colleagues suggested I do it, because I followed
what my colleagues do, because actually I did not do, I did not do, I
started to do, and have not done for a long time.  I followed my colleagues to do,
I saw that time I could not help but ask, always some d colleagues
better you do it, so do it is better to shoot it like that
.  So it's right at the end of the first one is just to do
დრო bridge ah very happy so we a lot of discussion.  Better tell
us not to go see it, then I better start that episode
and do and shoot like that.  We see on the face that you go to
interview people in the pattern, is it actually the same as when you went to interview people in the sister face before
, it's actually the same, just on the
face.  Yes, almost, OK, there is one I do not
host the show that thing, that is, I did not look at the camera with you I can not
say anything, actually no, so some people say watching
some videos this non-stop, how can non-stop, but it is actually good
, I think it is very natural to talk he is not, but
this is not planned, because I am really difficult
.  Do you have a bad resistance then?  Have to do it from above.  Resistance from
childhood resistance, so but again.  Some of the things you have to force yourself to do sometimes
.  What is that part that you see a need for?   It's
declining to the extreme, just now the director said that he has watched the follow-up
after not to
throw, then will not watch the episode again, so the episode decline
, so important to do one thing, that is, to supplement it, but
your thing is not a commercial supplement, that is, you are
actually what the framework will not have any special income, but the
result is that after doing this interview, it is
easier to ask him to do this thing
To supplement the oh, so this you start why would decide I think
first I, busy looking, the look YouTube videos
, doing entertainment things are getting less and less down, because
after the short videos, we take this, it will happen in the short films
I used to do many levels are very entertaining, but found that I
think everyone's patience is really less and less, is that we start
watching live
Another this I think the length of the film it becomes another utility this,
just like people used to read books.  So it will be raw pull maybe a few
days to read a book, and now through an interview, it is like
reading a book to know some special things in that field
, so I think you can do it, in fact, I like to
do talk without being angry.  So I think this moment the
time can be suitable to do it, because I am very
extremely problematic, but you are really very poor social no,
I think really I think again the reason is that I want to talk to people a day
this, I want to talk about something very falling, I do not want to talk about
something like money that sea
ñ that thing.  Followed a suddenly you can not write a person you
do not tell me good heart what the hell, so but it is a good one
called to
ask you some good de things, so I think this is like quite
myself at least quite fun to know before you do,
in fact, you have not said very black to think is that, this series
coming this episode I have to go in this direction,
I can ask this direction
The question, do you have a series like that, no series,
because I, I often I years ago um, because done three
years of it, I three years, the three years every month the video um.  I'm
good, that means my yield is very low, actually later.
Like YouTube people said, open to a certain point they
distribute troublesome, he said you stable out right, because at that time I
heard some friends say that they will soon their
subscriptions will rise, they are very stable out
videos.  So it's worth a week, so it depends on what's going on
in the market when they're like that.  Then like I do
concerts during that time, because those actually d yeah, mainly are to
see them have something to do before they will put a promotional surprise out
so that is very envious of those yeah those early years, that
is he that is anytime he can find someone to do it, I
can not I also do not know them.  To have them have something to promote
I do it, so every week done one does not have a good
series, the alone do so.  But in my eyes it seems to want to
hire whoever feels, I was watching I was watching when I clicked in
, wow Chao Wei, wow, then it just so happened to him shooting golden fingers and
work things, that is, there are movie photos, in fact, those
interviews have people you want to tangle, but he has not had a movie
promotion, but actually you want to hire behind your back.  Photo
does not
beat him know, the eldest brother did and really nothing.  Want to or
ignore the field not I myself like Dawn.  But I also don’t want to
be him.  why  Some have done you do not like it,
will become useless so, I Star Trek I have done several times
really, because but did not shoot it, oh young has done it, that is,
east to do it, in fact, done all,
Hong Kong people have done all you still want to be a person,
is strong.  That I'm great will practice all the English for him so
he does other on Hong Kong, I want to do everything I want to do it
So what about your thinking?  To choose this person on whether he
has anything on in the near future.  Do you need to upwith yourself yourself
may be good for that matter?something to want in the near future is.  Interview
opportunities that interview him to ignore those things, in fact, most do so do what
they want to ask, so with my colleagues, that
I help me talk together at the same time.
What kind of person is he?  Sometimes, if his that is not familiar with finding a few more
colleagues to talk to, what do you think is what find more people think is how to
see him, what kind of people he has, how he will see him, fight him hate him
or like him, that is, take more of such things, to.  So
if you invite that guest before maybe you will have a
list so yeah, when I choose this one, he is
usually your host to more, or is your
teamate will go to more D frame.  Half not half half
half not a lot, yes, wait a minute
what are you doing?  I'm very own I'm not very concerned about the market, want to
ignore the market, so I thought there is an interview purpose this,
in fact, is really to ask something I'm interested in the purpose,
should not be something the audience wants to know, such as maybe starting
quite big some people around me have
so I realized that cancer faces a lot of things
.  So I actually want to interview some related issues.  But I
know if I ask at the beginning, then this, it's like everyone
won't be too serious we haven't entered.  So I thought before that
time I on maybe an episode I was looking for some people that we are
interested in, maybe yeah lungs that will, but I at the end I want to
go away that, that is that I am interested in the purpose of it.  But
I'm still leaving, I'm having some difficulty, because maybe
recently, I've released a few episodes there's one episode of it.  It's asking an
AI, actually I'm not I want to know yeah, so I asked a see
I see lobster huh.  That's already a bad reaction,
so sometimes I ask alone whether I should
ask something I want to know at the beginning regardless of the audience.  Let him know
that this show is what it is, so you come and watch, or
I have to, I am very strategic to find
a little star something star first, then slowly walk into the
position, but I eventually actually want to really ask myself what I want to ask
, yes.  So you have to you have to prepare, there must be a bad frame
right eh, yes, yes, but this involves
, because the visit is no longer not so much need benefit so you see is it
necessary to
see no more people?  So this is how we do quantity
balance.  But actually you think if anyone sees good or bad if
, actually that is a letter to consider it.  Yes, so
I on I sometimes here, so I cheat before exam I went on the
program of Golden City to do an interview, in fact, before this I often
tell some colleagues, alas really appreciate Golden City very envious of him.  To
ask something with such depth, and someone is watching.  But when
I talked to you I realized that you have a little and have to consider
things that hurt your karma.  All of them.  So a little bit is I see you
well, but after finally understanding, you actually have to face back to the
business thing.  I initially interviewed a lot of Mo later it.
Uh, I've done some social work on my side.  Yes, I
have done social workers people social workers for yeah, middle-aged and elderly services that things, I have
done actually I want to like to do that.  Yes, only
you can do wonderful it, so that the reaction will compete છે
But I see that there is actually a
cheat is there is a design in it is you yourself this actually want to
do that one thing, but you will be very balanced market
test first.  So at the beginning, I will interview people first
, and then slowly leave him in, you think this one thing
is still not important, that you have a
message itself, you want to make through these such
arrangements, it will become a human
body program.  I think it's still interesting, but I sometimes I
do not want to be so purposeful, I sometimes do the show, because if
this since it is no longer a money-making show, I
want to be arbitrary, in fact, at least and I will not go to the place,
is stillpeoplemade
Lloyds I will not Lloyds or flow to
interview a people, because I think actually
every interview interview him, in fact, I want to respect the guests  I
can't focus on it, and I don't want to make everyone
more of a person, more recognition of his values
oh so, either, I find a people to come
, I plug him, but I do not want to be so happy right.
But that's why I wouldn't do that kind of thing.  I would I would also
wonder, actually, when you go to invite a guest
, what prwork you have in the middle.  That is, for example, if
you want to know Jincheng, please actually, wow your
show is a superstar.  So you you and the superstar to
invite, in fact, you will not say there is a way, or there is a is
you will text or call
, or still will ask the scriptures right
in fact, you are such as Fargo if not he has a.  The movie is
30 years old. I haven't done it. I won't do it. I'll take the initiative.  Uh, those are
.  That would suddenly he went from crazy to not so crazy cute so so
he and so, but it did not, and at that time maybe a
hundred some happened it, something so would feel like the
timing for him to do it.  So half of it doesn't have any special
medicine test.  So then is it that you are taking the initiative to be responsible for the contract, and then
then see if he chooses not to mean and now it is not at the beginning
and now will be quite a lot is.  What people will come to ask it so to license it
, that is what I am coming to do right interview right interview, what so do not
do, have become a not to mention the promotion machine, that is that that
, that is, some people have something to do so, so
you do not talk to do, find him think not done so.
Will do that in my part I actually want to steal a sneak peek,
because actually inviting people to do interviews this thing
is actually new to our station.  So I when I invite you
.  Will you so sharp, you that.  I'm not poisoning my feet
, I'm myself all the way.  So you you do not understand the
workings of the entertainment industry.  Yes, actually, as long as the person has a
movie and a song out you take the initiative to find him is the number he will if your
platform more people see mostly can so we count some
opportunities to ask or he himself will take the initiative to come already
It's an existential problem, that's if he doesn't have anything to promote,
mostly 4 or six You wouldn't say DM him like that you
DM him here if I know him I will
if I don't know him I have to choose an episode
That is to find a reason he does what I go through family this so he can say
I understand I understand them sometimes do not want oh that to
protect the other person to reject your space is, are a little
is not want to go there an excuse ok yeah understand because sometimes I have
I have to excuse, that is.  Well, you guys went and invited it.
Of course, there will be a lot of work among you
, how is that preparation for
inflation actually starting beforehand? For example, the inflation first.  I think what was said to Jincheng
, actually.  Asked how people around him
feel, so do not ask how to feel about him, but here
passed mostly this around the personal feeling is the feeling of the audience Hmm, the
feeling of the audience, sometimes less white monster, and some
things actually you know you ask him actually make the recipient
ask, or they these you can use a very light
very after curious really.
In short, you that is you are this much frame, well we asked me the
number is the lowest is my figured out things, the character will be no
infringement, but also I did not come on purpose, that you have been
doing this circle for a long time, so you sucked a lot all the way
, understand Hong Kong culture.  So but because I asked back I
used to actually I'm not really interested in circles or cultural things
specifically, so I have to do research
to do more.  Do you need it beforehand?  For example, you have to think of
something?  I think it would be such a favor OK?If
I think programs I would.  But I think the interview, I think that
natural occurrence is the most important, so why I, I
have your situation at the beginning, is there are some problems, what he said is not
interested, in fact, he I was not listening to think about a question
, because you have a layout, but actually quality a good
interview, actually everyone in the talk.  Um, so
I had a little left of that.  You are completely taking them to be people
, you have.  I have a little that when really nothing to ask the time
has not yet so have OK?
I enter the
process, if people are known, then I do not know, if
not know I have to have.  Jin this what you are like have just
said it will talk at the same time like that, and then do not
think anything about it.
But it appears that you talk about questions, some questions, but the
other person may not answer an answer, or some may not be there.
When fighting
you drill eyes, in fact, the best high form is is everyone
.  Everyone is very interested in doing this, we that
interaction is very there to be able to return energy to each other instead of hitting each other
, in fact, it is easy not to see, and it is also easy for him a few things
, so you and I am not a very sharp more
.  In fact, we feel that the other person is avoiding
something, we talk, in fact, you will know that he is avoiding that.  So
you have to ask the next question, then you think again, so it will appear just now
your situation will appear, that is actually asking looking at you
, actually I'm thinking about the second and third, that is a little
separate, and listen to you and have to think about
how the flow is I want to say that there may be a flow
is actually a good thing, the reason is today, if a person goes to
interview him, there are 10 media.  And 10
media, if in our way very very straight
to this, all the same thing,
see one already framed, so so I think if there is a remember
or the fold is actually good because there is a feature, my
example 247, that is bli d interview, so
some people will ask, every time ask, which Kowloon or
Hong Kong do you think this question is good, that is,
But I think it's actually good, because their interview model is
from childhood to grow up, actually a growing dragon shrink
, so he does have a very clear so the audience knows even if he ten
times, he this is his characteristic, style separated from something
, so it's very funny, I think.  I'm my own
program, I go to work, actually
I'm extremely dependent on the team, that is, for example, you, that
Aqiao has contacted you so, in fact, his role is to
help me build it, that is, I certainly I will
have a degree of understanding of you, so right, will go to the right
, but his work is he will help me find a deeper layer
, maybe even deeper
You have to read the book to read it, that is, for example, we have all gone to find
your book out, and why do this?  I was
talking to Ah when I said actually, the deeper my bottom
or the more able to have some back, I may not discuss
those things, I can be understanding, in fact, you will not
actually in different bodies, in fact, have said something many
times, you will not, will not be interested in talking again ah.  At the same
time, I have I have realized that actually I
myself do the interview when this, I will feel
like you just said, maybe he is avoiding this topic
, or he may this one he can not, so of course
you and I will maybe attack once more first, maybe I guess the
second time is not so, I was thinking.
Yeah is there actually a preall and then
communicate beforehand, yours is one so I recorded to
both think it seems very expensive people people are being
interviewed, because the most do so much homework
ct over so, I wonder if this step is actually
toomuch, or what you will see.  We
, others I think probably won't, yeah, some
very busy very busy people may not, so actually you
now look back at your series did so many episodes?
Can you find the location?  That you can not
say oh, we are a word our series is
doing this, there is a more likely mature d perspective to talk about those
things say those things like that, but that interview is
actually really already said just now, is already this
threshold to say really not high.
In fact, will many people do?  That is actually very similar five years ago,
I don't know why actually why it would be so much.  I did five years ago
actually I would have thought.  La, valley, ತಿ, not
too much even.  That is, of course, some traditional bodies
are doing questions, but he may not shoot, shoot out is not actually
a lot, but you now actually you have been Agu Tian doing the search
, he did how many interviews, you think I one, I want to
say a question, is that may not be relevant, but my the
matter treated that
used to see
the interview with Wong Tsai.  They interviewed Chang Smoking at the time.  what about the different
one  That was a desire to express themselves, that was the best looking
, but do not know what to experience the society, then started
everyone to hide, not so electric themselves, afraid, say things that should not be
said, but for a while so a lot of people room actually
.  Not very good, because the view is this, but that before that
era, wow, today not visit.  So three who, that is,
three what people interview you are very important right, that is, the three most
electric class.  Oh, it's asking
Ginko, Sai is also as strong as the movie
Maiden won't hurt.  That is
how important Nip is high.  You remember and not you have to say it,
he was this too, but it was really scary.  Are
n’t they afraid of offending people in the room?  Is it that having such an electric class
person here instead makes my guest is very feel that the
safespace is very large, that is, he is more able to
sing used.  I think anyway there are points to the end and the end is
, and when you go out on the TV station, although that
today inadvertently called the night talk is very strong, so but I think there is a
face component, and then in the TV station and in the network
out, because the network can be really very unplanned.  You're right
, maybe because it used to be a TV station after all, it did
n't.  That will not immediately have will know an interview out
15 listen or he will be a netizen will just, you are
scolded anyway, in fact, so we all become
podcast, I see now more and more people
do it, in fact, when it is popular  It's
still started, it's been a long time, a
long time, that learning program, and they can be really
specialized issues, in fact, I envy them those very specialized
issues, not very entertaining really very knowledgeable is to learn to
interview a person doing exercise absorb what carbohydrates there are
people listen to it so, but Hong Kong has not gone, he is
always Hong Kong audience is a little, he has to ask all the
characteristics of Hong Kong
, actually really not, I will be intermittently I will
interview it, that is, invest in this and will interview it, doctors
will interview, that I want to diversify D is to give people a
sense of nutrition and knowledge, that I finally I and I can
and you should go together with the medical program to,
seriously do so, and make that more people see good.
testing, listening to so much on, have you thought
not only to listen with us on this look if good news we
can membership program, in this world of information explosion, even
opposition, abnormal research has initial wash, is to
establish a rational space for everyone to conduct process judgment.
If you don't know, hopefully a lifetimeਕੇ, so you
want to invite you in to decide the direction of this channel together
.  Members exactly what exclusive benefits, you can
influence this nearly million channel of the selection, the next
episode about what topic, you can vote first, and can directly
talk to us before the video to shoot this tell us
what angle you want, the link is placed in
the discription,
click in now, with us and listeners become
creators.  waiting for you
Because what about last year?  Heart City he actually he eh, mid-year, is it at the
end of the year, eh, make back that cowboy that month,
cowboy March so then I have learned about the date rod you that,
yes, you are thinking to implement this thing, but you
can not get it from the government, but you are very concerned
about this matter, so you have to go find your own
way, I think I will actually push it
Want to understand you in this regard, sorry that your biggest
struggle, know how you
overcome these things.  At that time,
because I like it, so I think Hong Kong now often
blow back the previous cultural IP of such things, I
myself like those martial arts comics besides, there are second d, that
very talk about family very interesting, very touching and Chinese
workers very sharp king's cowboy, so, I want to do back out
.  So I talked to him with the government, because I have no
experience, I ent not so, maybe not so good
.  How about watching incense?  Is not to say I have to do a what quite more
quite large event, quite large and small.
Even later I really do short animation, six minutes or so
he made it, that is, in me and I do not have this application
experience, I just say to you what I will do, I will do what do what,
relatively and can this will be very numerically asked you have
, you will use this thing to attract how many foreign tourists tired, the most
said these things this I do not know he can not do
Can be used to measure culture this thing, is not చి not right, you
do not do it does not have those things, but he will still ask the patriots
what, I do not know you did do not know, you do not know how
even Japan likes so much, you shoot Kowloon City, Japan
obedient what, but you have to actually try to do that thing
, slowly slowly slowly he will have some very wonderful questions
I really answered poorly, and then no, and I was lucky enough to
get back some commercial sponsorship later on, that is, face to face plus.  How
many brands have appeared?  Three or so of it, yes
, that is the brand of shoes, there are some darts walking it
, that I see I have a tram, you ask the middle of the cold play there
is no small set
to this thing has so?  Good try not to hinder as but they
do not say to you to submit a KPI such a business world flip does not.
There is a very detailed question of what you want what you want, but also my
money per people will be relatively less, maybe before doing with the
subway done the exhibition, some luck now actually cowboys
are, because someone has seen me do before some more
solid exhibitions, he thinks better than you do bigger, so then
asked me to go to the government to apply for
other business after failing
Do this right here.  I wonder if you are so tired?  Because
of me, I think a problem is this, now there may still be
some people will go to put money to maintain the articles, because those
people who drive money or marketing people are still
old, so but with time the property world, there is a forward
.  So those people who drive money, may not be interested in cowboys
, for him is the explosion of the ship gyroscope, so just tired more and more tired
is going to be more and more water, in fact, I, I also
have a frame to say, I like things, just now, I said those
few things, all will still have a group of core people to
like, that is, I did not expect,
but he is often not very much proposed
So mask, but like people, that is, like my
feelings are as kind.  And his those are big guys
suck people's, all of them, so that I will get a lot of
support, that I will really really no way not much, must
thank ah.  Drawed said let me he go he to thank.
What his invol looks like.  He has a painting, design PT him
let me go to some I have a run frame to the competition, so that
is the formal collection of money so that, there are some examples if, I ን
he wants him not to wash it so, then I said no ah do not want,
I have some numbers back to you to give back so, to do this
thing, but how do you continue to go down, is really difficult, this time I may
not know  There
is a very sharp one coming.  Brother you know the previous left circulation said
water pulse, is shocked Japan
if
you see a person like this in Hong Kong so you say something, you really have to
come to see yeah this this really have to come to see, I did before
I did not ask you to come to see.  There are some people in Hong Kong who are so great
.  That I always tell the truth, I'm not the
sharp one, I'm going to make your people for others to see
this thing, I'm very most photographed most up to do so he some of these times are
it.  So yeah, again the same out of the book, because his
book now with no buy network now are speculating on dollars.  Um I do not fire
, I now do the original for everyone to buy like that.  I can hear
this, in fact, both of them are creative base, ըըer plus base
, such as Dongguang sex, in fact, I heard you just now seems to
be for KPI yeah, double industry these words you will ask it
.  Yes, yes.  You only walk by and see you.  No.
Yes, it is true but at the same time actually as you know, a
creation, in fact, it somehow it has a commodity to it
.  How do you go about
cooking to more or still?  How do I get to Nuesu
business this one thing.  So for example, sex stars so you will have you in the
company you will see different projects right do
you need to say travel
me I went to the soil period run 120 kilometers so this is
my own days of wedding days of not so difficult sharp yeah so
difficult that
I want to do this, you this time that meaning
?  I feel because of covid and will some
situation, so that we will not set some goals, because
do not dare because it becomes too big that moment I think the
consciousness of the society needs this thing, so I want to do
, so I combine things I think this thing to do is helpful to the society
.  But this thing is actually good.  Well myself
, not for the audience at all, because for example, I did a lot of
content at that moment, women and then not underwear or those
, all of them, I'm someone on the audience a little more,
but I have to think, so how do I explain to my boss, because
no trade, we go to the soil in the future maybe eh each person's
entry fee is 50,000 dollars, maybe I have to spend 100,000 dollars.
And there must be a commercial post-right, unknown, at least, so I have to
explain to him, so I usually shoot things I at least have a
cam like this, that time only me and my other ter
person squeeze, we go through all the work ourselves.  It reduces
the cost the company has to pay.  Similarly, I try to find customers
, to support me in this matter, so fortunately
our company's sales is very sharp, so
they really found, that is, I spend 100,000, in fact, the boss is
very simple, we can not eat cheat, wow boss can not touch
him, boss his ji, I spend you 100,000 I help you find it
.  No boss will resist.  So you just know this
thing, I find that and not yet white, that I find that it
has a reward, so I already have the problem so then make the audience want to
see it this is my storytelling technique, so that and make the
audience seem to substitute and go together to this experience this thing, so this I can handle three parties  You are can I
define, that the Eastern star to decide whether to see the movement
able to value the society or is this one is your
biggest motivation.  The biggest yes but this is also my biggest
creative resistance.  Because when you want everything to be
meaningful then, in fact, many things the audience wants to see things are actually a
laugh, in fact, in fact, maybe the meaning of laughter
, but my own mind may be more D, become to install
everything can do so you measure my net time must be enough effort to
do this so is the most difficult I finished to put a
lot of things.  Maybe it's interesting,
maybe an audience likes it, there's a need I don't feel like I really want to
do it myself.  And he so this may actually be the force of resistance,
in fact, in Jincheng you would think that the resistance is helping you to think about it
.  Which means, for example, if you say that I have a very patient issue of the
gas issue of a society that I am most concerned about or that I would like to have an impact in this
society to some extent.  And I
have thought, in fact, I myself a illset my
own package is actually most suitable in this aspect is
impact this, this reason that you know endless
, that brought a lot of international situation, historical things this thing is
very interesting, because my wife, A talk about
he is a drug cheater, and his perception of me
is very logical old, very rational,
because he sees you
A lot here so count yeah, but always it is a subjective yeah
technique thing you can not say count count to 100 count to
100 accurate and then do and achieve success of this is I think
so you really do some of the safest things, do the safest
means you are not innovative, later I went to that I have a so
I everything broke when I went to the head and
I did not have any time  It looked like there was
a clock in place.  I was thinking that is
yeah, how can I make a work out during a period of social division may
not help such a large
thing, but know that a small part of the effort is to make everyone discuss
when pure I have to demonize you, I have to beat people is able to make a
judgment and discussion.  So for me, I do
n't think it matters, it doesn't matter if you eat up now.  The most important thing is to
do this, it will be very meaningful in the future Then
he gave me a great power to withstand pressure bear eh,
intentionally for as creators, if we
hope to make our creative life when, whether
eventually we will go to this step is not a necessary
process I do not know.  I think the most KPI will not have very
exciting results.  So you say maybe you do this show actually
want some viewers want to yeah, um my my opinion is to think back to
what the significance of that thing is you KBI if there is no that thing no
number this no flow, you give up.  Only you think that the
righteousness of believing that thing will sustain you all the way down, so I
think the righteousness is the biggest This is just doing the original Youtu
interview is said, you say you want to make videos to catch up
Very rigid personnel say that chasing people chasing results
is not impossible to catch up, because if the calculation is right, then
everyone can calculate that number, no one can calculate that number
.  Yes, that's the way it is, when you do you have to consider
and time your creative life and want to be on site, to
scaleup when, for example, you have to do people's rooms
or do fund-raising periods, so this one person can not do so
much, you have to communicate with the team, so then you
also have to go back to the company every day, you may have to the day
together with the boss by and I hope to take a
good thing to do.  But the creation of things is
actually better than the person you write every stroke, and then you
do that program effect, you want to create the effect,
when a team appears, actually it will be a little
different from what you have in your mind.  That is how can
your communication and you co-produce this one this one process
, whether there is, at first it feels wow, very difficult, and
then slowly an excessive to overcome to see this
.  That's so difficult, but Ka-should you put your performance on
yourself, you'll be better.  I'm difficult, I'm I'm
I'm difficult too, so come up with the question, but we all
think 100 is just the oriental sound.  Um, because I'm very
humane, of course, we read a hundred to see my things,
so if we have a new art, we can not accept
this thing right.  Because it is not the new oriental that is
two sides of the thing, so so I, I actually I am not a
very good virgin, so this is what I want I have to I have to
improve.  You have tried something yeah actually everything,
but it is not because now I think it is more economically bad now
.  That becomes the problem we face so many, the biggest problem
is the economic problem, because there is really little to say about it.  It turns out I
might start a new show I can't land, I will start when I
will think about the direction of this show has not first.  So I for
example our company so there is a called a program so, actually
, we have a colleague called LER, so he has a daughter the
daughter is very interesting, I think this in I look at a lot of
network platforms this means that we are more young, have not yet have
not have a daughter, that IG may be a lot of it, but
not yet, so it is a uniqueness so, I think it is better to
do this program
The number must be good, because people without children may not watch
, but the people who watch will be some very heavy people.
So ah Jincheng do you have some of the projects you usually scaleup in the company
so
, but you have to communicate yours to others, so that
it will maintain that Jincheng style of, and then
can up and then your sky will also be able to yeah and
because with me and working together while being together for the longest time is the most meaningful to
find a common purpose or something
Should it be it's not too difficult to do if there are some additional
squares like that so if you say do maybe those doctrines that things
so it becomes a lot of some very business considerations of things, I
think we
have a personal view in that position, or whatever is not so easy.  So you
first do the first episode when the human room that came out of that component
, is it you originally played in your own mind, talk about the first episode I
imagine that you will want it more and more
, you said, oh maybe the algorithm will need you to do more
exercises, or maybe that month to take the exam, evolve it,
so this one thing is eh how do you add this will I go with
review
, dare not, because of me, my approach to order, that is,
without it a lot of changes, the people I interview may
not interview a second time in the short term.  Um, so maybe from the candidates or
yes, how to present things have to think about it.  That
is before I did not, I did not want to leave on that thing, I was going
around, different places shot right, so is the
face-to-face thing is already a little changed the second thing of
um actually we discuss more questions that my participation will be a
little more, usually interview I will will hide a little of myself.
You do not enjoy this process of communication, that is,
enjoy with the team, to have to have to frame it is very
difficult to do everything alone, and make him feel that this thing
to be interesting, you say yourself to convince it right?  I
lately I'm learning that in the past I will be the same people as I immersed
, in
recent years I will sometimes specifically hire a couple of not I have not, so
in the face of you may talk to colleagues, you already know
different this you will be hard, but I will let him know and you
exist, because you are different from me, so you do not become
us again.  I'll deal with it that way, yeah, it makes me have something
new, yeah.  So will they slowly slowly slowly
slowly not dare to speak again?  I will, so I try to explain it
to you.  why?  What you gest.  No not yet
, this moment is not what I want, the always love we
and communication the same because, in fact, always to two circles, we
find the stacked position, then to slowly back the stacked position
, yes, yes.  But the hard process is hard even
I think he is hard because he was not us at that time
, so he, I hope he understands.  In fact, our company is
before doing we are doing those abnormal human talk
history that videos, from the beginning and during CO period is
my day alone in a room to think, how to
do, so then after thinking, I feel to up ah to
many talented people come in together to
sellup that thing to scale it, then I
found the first how to challenge
Towards actually many things cannot цыі.  Indescribable when
so what, so how do I go to put one to, I'm most afraid of
some moments is if I myself we
each will have our own ເທ frame Well you showed
up when, feed, can not son?  Can not gold can not
oriental and then you say not very good.  So the next question is why
not, that long-term if I can not
profile spend an explanation when it seems like
yes it turns out that the creation is actually really difficult to see to
, so there is a situation, maybe you have not faced, because
you are still your show.  If you have to face it is
you start to have a second D Mo before.  Oh oh, yeah, and there are two
circumferences.  So this is even more difficult, so now you see
well maybe our company is, I have I no TV, there is
white and Uncle Sam.  Rather different people, different styles to do their own
channel suck themselves different from their own people.
That way the situation is better, so he back I read back to your
interview um, actually he did why to break up so many companies is not to have
a company of not pressed down to all small companies to, but
each can independently play their own qualities.  But your
situation is your show that came from the show, it's still,
it's other people's cooperation ah so how do you end up solving the problem
eh, I force myself to be responsible for my own yes
, I have to explain it, that is, the design, maybe
ask so good, so I initially really intuitively good and not
good enough, but not enough and later not big enough for me
.  So I have to keep going.  Or
standing because this picture, so it is actually relative to you is should the somewhat
basic to say.  Although I won't say?  I won’t talk about objective
, I’ll talk about the direction of the core.  For example because my interview
is these two things, so everything to this thing amplified
other can
Can that at the end of that initial intention is what first?  And those
things, now that initial you protect this initial intention, actually
100 kinds of interpretation methods of so, but the initial intention is like that,
so you do not I say amplify that, but you use other
methods to make too things I can.  Yes, actually Imajo just said
this, is the language between our mutual communication, is to
say, what is your art for what first your art play is not thinking
of showing in it, the art play is in the
work there to caremoreabout that
function
, so that people can see you have played art that work
right, so so this, as function to function
If you make it beautiful under the function, then you do your best,
but if it appears, you must tick the function that
direction is right, there will be a violent one.
When he helped us design before, wow it was so ugly
.  Then there is no first row, that is, so the row is not
right and wrong, is the row, maybe you are wearing um beautiful
people and beautiful or not beautiful, the word is so big not beautiful um, in fact, to star
hard that can I think it is.  This one is my own to communicate
with my d to communicate quite a lot, I am slowly
touching out to find, it turns out that we communicate quite quite quite is, for example,
we do these solutions, we have to ign our
purpose is what first?  We have to show our own creation or is
we have to bring that information to the audience so if it
is later then maybe we set the
priority that we have to balance the information and
accurate to the highest.  Below make beautiful OK so again if there is no
conflict of up up when, you do not do both down to fall
behind.  It may not be impossible to combine, yes, you
, and found this, in fact, I was discussing the accuracy,
I did not go to everyone's choice.  Um people I handed it back to
everyone what was it like when it
arrived?  Actually it is going to be different from me if
you let me do it, I might have a little different difference,
but it meets the criteria, is it meets that core.  Then it
should melt, yeah, I feel wow, sometimes I
feel wow, and very श्च how I am.  Yes yes yes
yes.  We have a last one designated question of, is
yeah if once this, you have to execute the death penalty money, death penalty money
, in fact, anything can you can have a dream to yeah choose
food.  So ah I will want to know yeah, you are actually going to
go ahead you will head ah, good main course yeah dessert yeah,
how are you going to build the produce?   It's
rice with big bones, ribs?  Why is it
good? The bone-good middle-head shoe rice is delicious.  Is there any
special meaning?  Purely good food, have no say where to eat there
, but to however no clean up early your middle head good food, I
eat nothing light Chinese, because I do darts those cre of
I know.
I, I don't mind eating against it, spicy with chili oil, not good I
like to eat rice, in short, actually soup eat chili oil is that way
, that is accounted for it, ha.  Feeding is to have chili is.
Finally this bad so yourself so yeah
, today thank you sun Akin City and light first, so if you
want to pay attention to their self-talk, then you can go to these
socialmedia there to see it, so
today thank you sun is.  OK, thanks.  Thanks thanks private.